<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="configuration.xsl"?>

<!-- Put site-specific property overrides in this file. -->

<configuration>
	
	<property>
    <name>http.robots.agents</name>
    <value>zuso,*</value>
    <description>The agent strings we'll look for in robots.txt files,
    comma-separated, in decreasing order of precedence. You should
    put the value of http.agent.name as the first agent name, and keep the
    default * at the end of the list. E.g.: BlurflDev,Blurfl,*
    </description>
  </property>
  
  <property>
    <name>http.agent.name</name>
    <value>zuso-robot</value>
  </property>
  
  <property>
		<name>http.agent.version</name>
		<value>1.8</value>
		<description>
			A version string to advertise in the User-Agent header.
		</description>
	</property>
	
  <property>
    <name>http.timeout</name>
    <value>20000</value>
    <description>The default network timeout, in milliseconds.</description>
  </property>

	<property>
		<name>http.redirect.max</name>
		<value>2</value>
		<description>
			The maximum number of redirects the fetcher will follow when
			trying to fetch a page. If set to negative or 0, fetcher
			won't immediately follow redirected URLs, instead it will
			record them for later fetching.
		</description>
	</property>
	
	<property>
		<name>parser.character.encoding.default</name>
		<value>utf-8</value>
		<description>
			The character encoding to fall back to when no other
			information is available
		</description>
	</property>
	
	 <property>
    <name>db.parsemeta.to.crawldb</name>
    <value>zh</value>
    <description>Comma-separated list of parse metadata keys to transfer to the crawldb (NUTCH-779).
     Assuming for instance that the languageidentifier plugin is enabled, setting the value to 'lang' 
     will copy both the key 'lang' and its value to the corresponding entry in the crawldb.
    </description>
  </property>
	
	<property>
		<name>http.content.limit</name>
		<value>-1</value>
		<description>
			The length limit for downloaded content using the http://
			protocol, in bytes. If this value is nonnegative (>=0),
			content longer than it will be truncated; otherwise, no
			truncation at all. Do not confuse this setting with the
			file.content.limit setting.
		</description>
	</property>
	
	<property>
		<name>http.accept.language</name>
		<value>ja-jp,en-us,en-gb,en,zh,zh-cn;q=0.7,*;q=0.3</value>
		<description>
			Value of theAccept-Language request header field.
			This allows selecting non-Englishlanguage as default one to
			retrieve.
			It is a useful setting for search enginesbuild for certain
			national group.
		</description>
	</property>
	
	<property>
    <name>fetcher.server.delay</name>
    <value>1.0</value>
    <description>The number of seconds the fetcher will delay between 
     successive requests to the same server.</description>
  </property>
  
  
  	<property>
	    <name>fetcher.threads.per.host</name>
	    <value>5</value>
	    <description>This number is the maximum number of threads that
	      should be allowed to access a host at one time.</description>
	  </property>
</configuration>
